OK so let's look at what we have altogether OK.
好的，让我们看看我们有什么完全好的。
There is a small lonely stone cottage with a thatched roof beside a lake in the countryside.
在乡间的湖边，有一座孤零零的茅草屋顶的小石屋。
It has a little square window at the front and beside that a single wooden door with a narrow dirt path
它的前面有一扇小方窗，旁边有一扇木门，有一条狭窄的土路
that leads away toward the nearby village.
通向附近的村庄。
Maybe there's a village nearby.
也许附近有一个村庄。
Standing beside the cottage is a small scraggly tree and in the distance there's a bigger one behind
小屋旁边是一棵参差不齐的小树，远处有一棵更大的树
a row of hedges bigger what one means a tree because we just mentioned trees.
一排树篱更大什么意思是一棵树，因为我们刚刚提到了树。
So if we say one we know it's a tree a bigger one a bigger one behind a row of hedges an old potato
因此，如果我们说一个，我们知道它是一棵树，一棵更大的树，在一排树篱后面，一个更大的树，一个旧土豆
farmer lives here with his dog Linus.
农夫和他的狗莱纳斯住在这里。
It's my imagination.
这是我的想象。
It's a peaceful place again.
又是一个宁静的地方。
That's the atmosphere.
就是这样的气氛。
It's a peaceful place.
这是一个宁静的地方。
They sometimes go for walks along the lake in the evening when the weather is warm the sun setting over
他们有时会在傍晚天气暖和的时候沿着湖边散步，太阳落山
the water reminds the old man of strolls strolls means slow casual walks strolls he used to take with
水让老人想起散步
his wife before she passed away.
他的妻子去世前。
This is a very sad story I imagine.
这是我想象的一个非常悲伤的故事。
What's wrong with me.
我怎么了。
Why did I have to put that sad thing at the end.
为什么我要把那件悲伤的事放在最后。
Oh my goodness.
哦，我的天啊。
I have a real problem.
我有一个真正的问题。
So you can see how it all fits together.
所以你可以看到这一切是如何结合在一起的。
Before I mention my imagination I make sure to say the important details.
在我提到我的想象力之前，我一定要说重要的细节。
Then when I get into my imagination the sad story of this lonely man and his dog Linus lived by the
然后当我进入我的想象这个孤独的人和他的狗莱纳斯的悲伤故事
lake.
湖。
We like to reminisce and remember the old times sad story is first based on that description.
我们喜欢回忆和记住旧时代的悲伤故事首先是基于这种描述。
But you're now there with me in your mind right.
但你现在在你的脑海里和我在一起。
Because we've been through the description you have a clear picture first.
因为我们已经通过描述你首先有一个清晰的画面。
Then you're able to feel something when I actually describe what the man does.
然后，当我真正描述这个人的所作所为时，你就能感觉到一些东西。
The potato farmer that I invented that I imagine.
我想象的我发明的土豆农夫。
So that's the basic idea of describing things clearly.
这就是清晰描述事物的基本思想。
Again you can use it for lots of different situations.
同样，您可以将它用于许多不同的情况。
Not only describing houses they can use it for many different things you can use it to describe your
不仅可以描述房屋，还可以将其用于许多不同的事物，您可以用它来描述您的
dreams.
梦想。
You can use it to describe ideas you can use it to describe what you're looking at out the window what
你可以用它来描述想法 你可以用它来描述你在窗外看到的东西
you want somebody to buy at the supermarket.
你希望有人在超市买东西。
Description is one of the things at the very foundation of being able to express yourself in English
描述是能够用英语表达自己的基础之一
clearly.
清楚地。
Now your assignment to practice is to do the same thing.
现在你的练习任务是做同样的事情。
What I'd like you to do is find a picture of a house and then try to describe it in vivid very clear
我想让你做的是找一张房子的照片，然后试着用生动的非常清楚的方式来描述它
detail.
细节。
Make sure that you use several adjectives and make sure that you choose a main noun especially for the
确保你使用了几个形容词，并确保你选择了一个主要名词，特别是
first sentence.
第一句话。
Then after you do that and you've made a couple of clear sentences to describe what people can see to
然后在你这样做之后，你已经做了几个清晰的句子来描述人们可以看到什么
get a feeling for the place then imagine a story and add some interesting description in your story
感受一下这个地方然后想象一个故事并在你的故事中添加一些有趣的描述
that is based on based on your basic description.
这是基于您的基本描述。
OK so try this practice it you can do it for a couple of different things if you want to try a picture
好的，所以试试这个练习，如果你想尝试一张照片，你可以做一些不同的事情
of a person or if you want to try maybe something you just imagine that's fine but make sure that you
一个人，或者如果你想尝试一些你想象的东西，那很好，但要确保你
actually are doing something as a way to get comfortable with description because it's again really
实际上正在做一些事情来适应描述，因为它又是真的
really important.
真的很重要。